### Contact

aldeible@lghealth.org

www.linkedin.com/in/aarin-deibler-msn-rn-cen-ne-bc-0b906bb3 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Emergency Nursing Neuroscience Bariatric Surgery

## Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)

#### Certifications

Nurse Executive (NE-BC)
Certified Emergency Nurse (CEN)

# Aarin Deibler, MSN, RN, CEN, NE-BC

Nurse Manager at Lancaster General Health/Penn Medicine Lancaster, Pennsylvania

## Summary

I am a highly engaged nurse manager with 20 years nursing experience accross medical-surgical, critical care, and emergency-trauma settings. I integrate a servant leadership style of management into my practice, emphasizing collaboration and teamwork. I am a passionate advocate for the profession of nursing and ensuring positive patient outcomes.

## Experience

Lancaster General Health/Penn Medicine 21 years 2 months

Nurse Manager March 2018 - Present (2 years 5 months) Lancaster, Pennsylvania

Manage all operations and employees of an 18-bed Intermediate Intensive Care Unit

### Nurse Manager

June 2014 - March 2018 (3 years 10 months)

Lancaster, Pennsylvania Area

Manage all operations and employees of a 26-bed inpatient nursing unit

## **Emergency Room RN**

January 2001 - May 2014 (13 years 5 months)

**Emergency Department** 

ACLS, PALS, and ATCN certified to care for critically ill adults, children, and traumatically injured populations

#### Staff RN

June 1999 - January 2001 (1 year 8 months)

Transitional Care Center

Staff nurse in subacute inpatient nursing unit caring for a variety of medicalsurgical patients.

# Education

Eastern Mennonite University

Master's degree, Nursing Leadership & Management · (2013 - 2017)

Millersville University of Pennsylvania

Bachelor's degree, Nursing · (1997 - 2000)

Lancaster General College of Nursing & Health Sciences Diploma, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1997 - 1999)

Hempfield High School

· (1993 - 1996)